Andrew 你知道吗
Andrew, you know what?
我们没离婚的时候你就对我的成功不爽
You resented my success when we were married, okay?
但是现在这完全让你痛不欲生了
But now it is absolutely eating you raw.
你是他生命中最美好的事物 而他却离此而去
You were the best thing to ever happen to him and he threw it away.
对 你是我生命中...我是你生命中 最美好的事物
Yeah, you were the best thing-- I was the best thing
而你却离此而去
that ever happened to you and you just threw it away.
女士 如果你想跟Kent开 那个有关人质的会议 我们就该走了
Ma'am, we have to go now if you want to catch Kent for a hostages meeting.
好的 听着 我不会让你
Okay, listen, I will not have you
离间我和Catherine的
undermine me with Catherine.
你想要拿手包么? 我要
will you be wanting a clutch? - I will.
好的 我不要
Okay. - I will not.
噢 你不要么? 不 不 我要 我要包包
- Oh, you don't? - No, no, I will. I want the bag.
不 我要Catherine和我一起过感恩节
No, I want Catherine to spend Thanksgiving with me,
而不是随便一个男朋友
not some random boyfriend.
还有可怜的外婆怎么办 她最多可就能活到三月份
And what about poor Memaw, who's guaranteed to be dead by March?
如果运气好的话
With any luck.
好吧 恭喜你
Well, congratulations.
你成功的学会了怎么操控Catherine
You have successfully learned how to manipulate Catherine.
这怎么就侮辱到她了呢?
How is that insulting to her?
天哪 你这是完全颠倒黑白...好吧
God, you just turn it all around-- okay.
我挂了他的电话 我们走么?
just hanging up on him. - Shall We go?
好的 我们走吧 包里有几片Advil(止疼药)
- Yeah, let's just get out. - There's some Advil in the bag.
我希望我们也有职业杀手的电话号码
Yeah, I hope we have a number for a contract killer, too.
我愿意干
I'll do it.
车不错啊 Mike 新车么?
Nice wheels, Mike. This new?
也不算新 就像你娘一样
Not quite. Like your mother,
曾经被不少人爱过 他们都为她付了钱
it's been previously loved and paid for by a couple of guys.
我猜这意味着你的债还清了 对吧?
I guess this means you cleared your debts, huh?
不 我只是多欠了点
No, I've added this to my debt.
噢 是那种一路喝到不再醉的老方法啊
Oh, the old drink your way out of alcoholism approach.
我喜欢 不 这跟我喝酒的事可不一样
- I like it. - No, this isn't like when I drank.
你以前酗过酒?
You had a drinking problem?
没有那么严重 只是有点小瘾 都不算是酒瘾
Not a problem. Uh, an issue.
都不算是酒瘾 就是有一段很爱喝
Not even an issue. A hitch.
你曾经很爱喝酒?
You had a drinking hitch?
Dan 我欠了十万块
Dan, I owe 100 grand.
我做什么也改变不了这件事
Nothing I can do will change that.
所以呢 我接受我不能改变的东西
So, I've accepted what I cannot change.
再多几千块也没什么所谓
A few extra grand doesn't matter.
你现在是醉了么?
Are you drunk right now?
早上好 Egan先生 你看没看那篇地域主义的文章?
Morning, Mr. Egan. Have you read the regionality paper?
没有 好吧
No. - Okay.
祝你今天愉快
Have a great day.
老有人对我这样 不 没有
- I get that all the time. - No, you don't.
但是我得
But I need to talk
跟那个狗娘养的自闭土鳖谈谈
to that autistic lumberjack son of a bitch.
噢 他在这呢 你好啊 Kent
Oh, there he is. Hi, Kent.
副总统女士 我听说你在练普拉提
- Madam Vice President. - Hey, I heard you were doing Pilates.
我都不知道你还有身板呢
I didn't know you had a core.
我有 而且可硬朗了呢
I do and it's like steel.
那我们现在是真的没有行动么?
So are we really not doing anything
对人质的事
about the hostages now?
一点都没么? 我们有行动
Nothing At all? - We are Doing something.
是么? 那我们在做什么? 什么都没有
Yeah? What are We doing? - Nothing.
除非有足够的票数支持干预
Until the numbers support intervention,
我们能做的最多也就是什么也不做
doing nothing is the most positive thing we can do.
真高兴和你谈话 Kent
You know, it's just so great talking to you, Kent.
我就喜欢接近无为的感觉
I love being close to the inaction.
今天下午的国家安全会议还是要开的 对吧?
The national security meeting this afternoon is still happening, right?
是的 4:30 人质事件以及向以色列出售
Yes, 4:30. Hostages and the SM-17 missile defense system sale
SM-17导弹防御系统两件事都会讨论
to Israel will both be discussed.
SM-17d 还有个小写的d
SM-17d. There's a lower case D.
对不起 先生 细节很重要
- Apologies, sir. - Details are important.
小数点放错一位数就能杀死一位糖尿病人 是的 先生
- A misplaced decimal point can kill a diabetic. - Yes, sir.
我很期待像我们协商的那样参加会议
I look forward to attending the meeting as per our deal.
总统会很希望你在场的 我也是
POTUS would love to have you there, as would I.
前提是你能按时赶回来
That's if you can possibly be back in time.
从哪赶回来? 对不起 我8:45有个会
- Back in time from what? - I'm sorry, I have an 8:45.
Ryan先生 是的 先生
- Mr. Ryan. - Yes, sir.
什么? 不 Kent? 呃 女士
- What? Kent? - Uh, ma'am.
什么? 你要去倾听乡音...
Yes? - The Listen to Rural America program
你在中期选举后答应总统说的
that you okayed with POTUS after the midterms is looking--
你知道吗 你能不能穿上跑鞋
You know what? Why don't you put on your running shoes
然后他妈赶紧给我跑到重点! Jonah
and get to the fucking point, Jonah?
今天北卡罗州的猪肉委员会有选猪比赛
The North Carolina Pork Board is having a pig picking today.
听起来很古典 Kate Middleton会去么? (英国王妃)
Sounds classy. Will Kate Middleton be there?
总统希望你能出席
POTUS would like to get you down there
用你的亲和力去大展美国嘿
and utilize your people skills to kick off U.S., Hey.
是就准备叫这个名字么? 是的
- That's what they're gonna call it? - Yeah.
谁想出来的狗屎名字啊?
Who came up with that incredibly shitty name?
正是在下 女士
That would be me, ma'am.
好吧 他们想让我去猪肉烧烤会上
Okay, so they want me to go to a pig roast
见一群可能会在烤猪之前
to meet a bunch of men who probably took turns
轮流干那头猪的人么?
to fuck the pig before they roasted it?
我觉得他们不会轮流的
I wouldn't presume they took turns.
我告诉你 我要参加4:30的那个会
Let me tell you something. I'm going to that 4:30 meeting
就算我要让Sue像超人那样
even if I have to get Sue to fly around the world
反着绕地球飞一圈让时间倒流
the wrong way like Superman and reverse time.
你明白吗? 是的 女士
- Do you understand that? - Yes, ma'am.
好的
Okay.
女士 我父亲的病情突然恶化了
Ma'am, my dad has taken a turn for the worse.
我想这个选猪比赛是个很好的机会...
I'm thinking this pig picking is a good opportunity--
噢  是的 你不用去了 去陪你爸吧
Oh, yeah, skip it. Skip it. Go to him.
我会给你带三明治还有六趾老公回来的
I'll bring you back a sandwich and a six-toed husband.
也许如果她换个机场着陆的话... Gary
Maybe if She landed At a different base-- - Gary.
这不是你的专长领域
This is not your area of expertise.
就是往日历上打字而已
It's just typing into a calendar.
对不起 Sue 你的工作非常有难度
I'm sorry, Sue. Your job is really difficult.
打扰一下? 你的工作非常有效率
excuse me? - you do It very efficiently.
Gary 谢天谢地啊
- Gary. - Oh, thank you, Jesus.
我们得走了 咱们得去跟乡巴佬们打成一片了
We got to go. We're gonna go mix with the hicks.
Furlong众议员打过电话来 他希望和您面谈
Congressman Furlong called and he'd like some face time.
好吧 我想一下 那我宁可在我的木耳上点一把火
Okay, well, let's see, I'd rather set fire to my vulva.
意思就是不干 他现在四处扮好人
- So that's a no. - He's in town trying to play nice
是为了明年左右要竞选参议员 不是吧?
for a possible Senate run in The next year or so. - Seriously?
Roger Furlong扮好人 就跟马龙白兰度演红发少女似的
Roger Furlong trying to play nice is like Brando trying to play Annie.
这个笑话不错 Mike
That's a good one, Mike.
谢谢 女士 等一下 女士
- Thanks, ma'am. - Wait. Ma'am?
我刚收到一条短信
I just got a message here. Something about a paper
说你女儿写的 一篇文章上了某个人的博客
that your daughter wrote that ended up on some guy's blog.
看吧 这就是为什么天朝要管理 大内网的原因 文章说什么了?
See, this is why China regulates their Internet. What does it say?
我不知道 电影研究课的论文什么的
I don't know. Some film studies course. A paper she wrote.
你知不知道我一年得付那家学校6万5?
Did you know that I'm paying 65 grand a year to that school?
他们应该是要往爆米花上洒金子才对的是吧?
They had better be putting gold on that popcorn instead of butter, right?
噢 女士! 怎么了? 噢 不要啊
- Oh, ma'am! - What? Oh, no.
我要走了 我要跟您一起去
- I'm out of here. - I'm coming with you.
什么? 总统希望我去监测美国嘿
What? - Potus wants me to monitor U.S. Hey
因为是我的宝贝项目 噢 我嘞个苍天啊
- as kind of my pet project. - Oh, for fuck's sakes.
这肯定是你第一个没有动用麻醉药
This must be the first pet project of yours
搞来的宝贝项目
that didn't involve resorting to chloroform.
是的 那都是以前的事了 Mike
Yeah, well, it's early days, Mike.
你能处理Catherine的事么?
Can you take care of this Catherine business?
我有地方要去 哪啊?
- I've got someplace I've got to be. - Where?
呃 我想我找到接近Kent Davison的办法了
Well, I think I might have found a way to get to Kent Davison.
如果你要杀了他娘然后穿她的皮的话 那严格来说可是犯法的哟
If you kill his mother and then dress in her skin, that's technically illegal.
严格来说
Technically.
副总统办公室现在正为
The veep's office is pumped
新外交政策摩拳擦掌呢 先生
about the new foreign policy portfolio, sir.
我刚看了一篇很有意思的文章
And I read this really interesting paper
说为什么地域主义是比国家主义
on how regionality
更加坚实的政治基础
is actually a more significant political prism than nationality.
你是不是刚加入这家普拉提班啊 Egan先生?
Did you just join this Pilates studio, Mr. Egan?
是的 这里很方便
Yeah. Yeah, you know, it's convenient.
你住哪? 附近
Where do you live? - Nearby.
就是...这一片
Local to here.
我听说人质的事愈演愈烈了
I hear the hostage situation is really heating up.
希望你以前做过普拉提
I hope you've done Pilates before.
人们总以为自己随便就能上这些机器
People think they can just get on one of these machines.
不 我练了六个月才开始用这个的
No. Six months I did before I got on this.
是啊 我永远都着眼长远目标
Yeah, well, I'm all about the long-term goals.
Mike 看这个
Mike, look at this.
看这个 Mike
Look at this, Mike.
我在空军二号喝咖啡哟
Just sipping some coffee. Air Force Two.
非常好 帮我照张望向窗外的照片
Real good. Take a picture of me looking out the window.
Jonah Jonah 你冷静
Jonah. Jonah, calm down.
这只是一架带标致的飞机而已 又不是星际过山车 (迪士尼乐园项目)
It's a plane with a logo. It's not Space Mountain.
你要是上了空军一号怎么办? 在座位上打飞机么?
What the hell do you do on Air Force One, rub your dick on the seats?
我还没有上过空军一号
I haven't actually been on Air Force One.
啥? 我还没有...
- What? - I haven't been--
Oh!
女士 呃
- Ma'am. - Ugh.
你怎么样 Mike? 挺好的 女士
- How you doing, Mike? - I'm doing great, ma'am.
听说你的财政情况了
Heard about your financial situation.
船什么的
You know, the boat and everything.
没事的
It's fine.
我已经改换了我唯一能改变的东西
I've changed the only thing I can--
我对事物的反应
my reaction to things.
噢 希望你偶尔也改换一下你的内裤
Oh. And your boxers occasionally, I hope.
我现在每天换一条
I have a fresh pair every day now.
噢 不错不错 Mike
Oh, good for you, Mike.
女士?
Hey, ma'am?
什么 Gary? 出什么事了?
What, Gary? What's wrong?
我知道你觉得我这人大惊小怪 女士
I know you think I'm melodramatic, ma'am.
我知道你就是大惊小怪
I know you're melodramatic.
我们刚玩完了
Uh-huh. Our world has just ended.
Mike!
看这个
Read this.
这是什么?
What is this?
揭秘: Selina的小暗号
Selina's secret stash of signals.
当副总统揉自己的右耳时 她的助手
When the VP rubs her right ear, an aide will tell her
就会告诉她必须要接紧急电话
she has an important call that she must take.
在不愿谈话的时候 这是她的抽身之策
In an unwanted conversation, this is her exit strategy.
好吧 现在有人维基解密了暗号
All right, well, somebody WikiLeaked the code.
我们不能再用这些了 我们需要新的暗号
So we can't use those. We need new signals.
那些暗号是花了好久才摸索出来的
Those signals took years.
我不能把秘笈撕了
I can't just tear up the gestictionary
然后瞬间发明一套新暗号
and come up with new codes like that.
好吧 这个就可以做一个暗号 类似静音什么的
Okay, that could be a signal. Kind of a silent click.
你能不能...好么 你就...
Would you please-- okay, could you just--
我只是需要一些最基本的暗号应付今天
I just need something basic for today.
我不想困在那跟那些
I don't want to get stuck talking pig shit
把干草垛当家具的人谈论什么猪的破事
with people who use hay as furniture.
我需要一个
I need an exit strategy
能让我4:30回华盛顿 的抽身计策 赶紧给我想
to be in DC by 4:30, so start thinking.
好吧 但是这些新暗号必须要隐蔽
Okay, but we have to make these new signals subtle
要看起来不像是在打暗号
so they don't kind of look like signals.
你明白就是这样
You do realize that that was the point
以前才要有暗号的吧? Mike 我意识到了
- of the old signals, right, Mike? - I realize that.
噢! 你可以拍手
Oh! You slap your hands together.
然后竖起大拇指
Kind of give it a little thumbs up.
不行 这个就像是我拍死了一只虫子然后说
No, that's like I squished a bug
我拍死了只虫子真酷!
and then I said, Oh, it's so cool I squished a bug.
那你拿着电话挠头呢?
What if you scratched your head with your phone in your hand?
这个怎么样?
What about this?
哦 不行...
Oh. No...
这样看着不好看 噢 那算了
- You don't look pretty. - Oh, forget it.
我想到了 你可以揉眉毛
I got it. You can rub your eyebrow.
不会有人注意到的 很隐蔽
No one will see that. It's subtle.
很自然
It looks natural.
那如果别人觉得我眉毛长阴虱了呢?
What if people think I have crabs in my eyebrows?
眉毛怎么能长阴虱呢?
How can you have crabs in your eyebrow?
好吧 Gary 当一对男女非常相爱
Okay, Gary, when a man and a woman
又是这个男人生日的时候...
love each other very much and it's the man's birthday--
出事了 什么?
- Crap in a hat. - What?
是你女儿 什么? 出什么事了?
- It's your daughter. - What? What is it?
她没事 不过她干了一些会让你想杀了的事
She's fine, but she's done something that'll make you want to kill her.
天哪 到处都是了
Christ, it's everywhere.
如果只是篇电影论文的话...
Well, if it's just a film studies essay--
不 Catherine的论文是写
No, Catherine's essay is about
Emad Burnat的 5台破相机的
Emad Burnat's movie 5 Broken Cameras.
如果没有Owen Wilson演出的话 我可能就不知道这片
If Owen Wilson's not in it, I probably don't know it.
这是一部关于巴勒斯坦人非暴力抵抗
It's about nonviolent Palestinian resistance
以色列人在(约旦河)西岸建立定居点的电影
to Israeli settlement on the West Bank.
这听起来不像是Owen的片子
That doesn't sound like one of Owen's.
她在文中说这是对以色列
She talks about the masterly portrayal
野蛮非法入侵的精湛写照
of brutal, illegal Israeli aggression.
哎呀 我们必须发布声明
Ouch. - We have to issue a statement.
好的 声明要用标准的挺以色列
All right, well, standard issue pro-Israeli,
也挺巴勒斯坦的口气 但要稍微偏向以色列一点点
pro-Palestinian, but subtly more pro-Israeli statement.
你就按F9把这破玩意打印出来就完了
I mean, hit F9 and print that fucker out.
不 这必须好好写
No, this needs to be top-notch.
这必须是滴水不漏
This needs to be the Gettysburg Address
毫无破绽 说了当没说的东西
of tightrope-walking, say-nothing bullshit.
我大显身手的时候到了
My time has come.
好吧 这样我们下次选举就输掉佛罗里达好了 (退休犹太人的天堂)
All right, well, next election I guess we lose Florida, then.
我们15分钟后着陆
We got wheels down in 15.
好吧 我得换衣服了
All right, I've got to change.
好吧 我给Amy发短信
All right, I'll text Amy.
Gary 我今天要穿什么?
Gary, what am I supposed to wear today?
至少这个没问题
At least that's good.
大家好呀
Well, howdy, y'all.
我的天哪 看看这里
Oh, my goodness. Look at this.
走得透 聊着肉
Walking the walk, talking the pork.
看看你 拿着棉花糖的成年女人
Look at you, a grown woman with cotton candy.
像你的脸一样粉嘟嘟的 你们两个我都要抱一下
Pink like your cheeks. I'm gonna give you both a hug.
天哪 这看起来好吃得要舔手指了
Oh, gosh, that looks like finger-licking fun.
这是我今天刚想到的说法哦 你们喜欢吗?
That's a term I just coined today. Do you like it?
每个人都过得很高兴 但是这位小伙子
Everybody's having such a good time. But this young man
怎么没有东西吃呢? 为什么呀?
doesn't have anything to eat. Now why would that be?
我希望你不要饿死了哟 甜心
I hope you're not just starving to death, sweetheart.
出什么事了? 我们应该让你多长点肉才行哦
What's going on? We've got to get some meat on your bones.
这样就好了
And there you go.
你一开口就能实现
Ask and you shall receive.
为什么只有我一个人带着牛仔帽?
Why am I the only one wearing a cowboy hat?
我要摘了这顶帽子
I'm gonna take this hat off.
不行 头发被帽子压过了 千万不要
No. Hat hair, hat hair. Please don't.
是的 她在肉前面表现得很好 先生
Yes, she's pressing the flesh very well, sir.
而这帮人有很多很多肉
And these people have a lot of flesh.
政治上两个要绕着走的事:
Two things in politics to avoid--
中东问题 还有家庭争吵 现在我们这是二合一了?
Middle East and family strife. And we're combining both?
你得让他女儿道歉
Now you get the daughter to apologize.
你有我的授权
You have my authority.
也就是说你有总统的授权
Ergo, you have POTUS's authority.
明白了么? 是的 先生
- Understood? - Yes, sir.
如果现在是60年代的话
If this were the '60s,
我们可以直接派国民警卫队把她女儿干掉
we could just have the National Guard shoot the daughter.
白宫的 白宫的 让一让 借过
West Wing, West Wing. Pardon me. Coming through.
噢 你好 不好意思 白宫的 过一下
- Oh, hi there. - Pardon me, West Wing. Pardon me. Excuse me.
你好 小姑娘 我是总统办公室的
Oh, hello, little girl. Office of the president.
请站开 谢谢
Please step off to the side. Thank you.
女士 我接到授权通知您
Ma'am, I have been charged with informing you
您必须让您的女儿Catherine
that you need to get your daughter Catherine
立即明确的道歉
to apologize unequivocally and immediately.
是么? 你去死吧 竹竿
Yeah? Well, go shit yourself, Long Tall Sally,
我会按我自己的时间
because I will deal with my daughter
用我自己的方式来管我女儿
in my own way on my own terms.
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
噢 这是你妈 嘿 你接通她了?
- Oh, here's your ma. - Hey, you got her?
嗨 Catherine 你好吗?
Hi, Catherine. How are you?
妈妈好 住手 住手 你吓到我了
- Hi, Mom. - Stop it. Stop it. You're freaking me out.
住手 吓到你了?
stop it. - Freaking you out?
不 亲爱的 不是你  Catherine
No, honey. Not you, Catherine.
是Mike 他把你放在了他身上
It was Mike. He had you on top of his body.
不 这个说法不对劲
No, that came out wrong.
听着 你过得怎么样? 我挺好
- Listen, how are you doing? - I'm okay.
我受到了很多人注意
I'm getting a lot of attention.
是的 你为什么要戴牛仔帽啊?
Yeah. - Why are you wearing a cowboy hat?
我在出席一个肉类活动
I'm at a pork event.
听着 你不能跟任何人说这篇论文的事
Listen, you can't talk to anybody about this essay.
媒体 记者什么的都不行
No media, no journalists or anything.
有人在你那边么 亲爱的? 是谁?
You have somebody there, sweetie? Who is that?
是的 是我男朋友
Yeah, actually, it's my boyfriend.
开玩笑吧 真让人激动
You're kidding. That's exciting.
他叫Rahim 他是Dilka的弟弟
His name is Rahim. He's Dilka's brother.
Dilka的弟弟?
Dilka's brother?
什么? 你觉得他是伊朗人有问题么?
What? Do you have a problem with him being Iranian?
好吧 Catherine
Okay, Catherine, you know
你知道我不是种族主义者
that I am not a racist, okay?
我大学的男朋友有四分之一Cherokee血统呢 (北美原住民的一支)
My boyfriend in college was a quarter Cherokee.
妈妈 很对不起 但是我不会道歉的
Mom, I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna say sorry.
好吗? 不 Cath...
- Okay? - No, Cath--
Catherine 别...好吧
Catherine, don't-- all right.
好吧 真顺利 和Catherine聊得不错?
- Well, that worked perfectly. - Good talk with Catherine?
这个嘛 我们有比这个聊得好的时候
Well, we've had happier conversations.
比方说我告诉她她外公去世了的那次
Like when I told her her grandpa had died.
噢 她不喜欢他吧?
Oh, she didn't like him, huh?
不 我说的不是这个意思
No, that's not what I meant.
噢 对不起 只是我外公 他真是个变态...
Oh, sorry. It's just my grampy, he was a real prick.
好了 Mike 我是说他...
- Okay, Mike. - I mean he was--
你得去弄架直升机
You need to get a chopper.
我要你去Catherine的学校
I want you to go to Catherine's college.
不 你接上她 然后把她带到空军基地
No. You pick her up, bring her to the air base. All right?
弄点毛巾 我可能要对她管教管教
Get some towels. I may need to daughter board her.
好么?
Okay?
你讨厌直升机 Mike 我知道
- You hate choppers, Mike. - I know.
我总是害怕把我脑袋削掉了
I'm always afraid I'm gonna get my head cut off.
是啊 有这种事
Yeah, it happens.
当以色列军队没有占领...
While Israel's military non-occupation--
不 不 在场
No, no, presence.
当以色列军队在场时 如何如何如何
While Israel's military presence-- words, words, words.
噢 扮高兴这个事太他妈累人了
Oh, this whole being pleasant is fucking exhausting.
是的 先生 非常累人
Yes, sir. It's very tiring.
我对这些烂人们已经说不动好话了
I'm running out of nice juice to spray at these shit munchers.
你好啊 见到你很高兴
Hi there. Good to see you.
我们同时也希望能让巴勒斯坦人能建立起家园
We also desire a settled homeland for the Palestinian people.
看看是谁啊
Oh, look who we have here.
不光是大美女 还有大美女哦
Not only Ginger Rogers, but also Ginger Rogers.
这个梗堆得好 先生
Nice joke construction, sir.
不要拍我的马屁了 你个四眼废柴
Stop trying to polish my dick, you fucking four-eyed failure.
好吧 然后...
- Okay. - And--
朋友们好啊 我们正好在楼里 就顺道过来了
Greetings, friends. We were just in the building, so we stopped by.
在楼里? 好吧 你们今天是来擦窗户的么?
In the building? Okay. What, are you guys washing the windows today?
还是来打扫卫生间? 你真是聪明啊 Dan
- Working on the bathrooms? - You're quite the wit, Dan.
是的 我是聪明 而你就是...
Yeah, I am quite the wit. And you're quite--
我们正要去医院
We were just heading to the hospital.
我父亲的呼吸现在很糟糕了
My father's breathing has become very bad.
他们觉得他可能过不了今晚
They think he might not last through the night.
而Dan要跟我一起去好接着起草声明
And Dan needs to come with me so we can continue the statement.
很抱歉 噢 完全没有的事 你爸的事我很遗憾
- Apologies. - Oh, no, not at all. I'm sorry about your dad.
好了 我们该走了 那下次再谈
- Okay, we should be going. - We'll talk another time, then.
我有的是时间
I got all the time in the world.
事实上我们必须在明天之前离开特区
We do actually have to be out of DC by tomorrow.
那只是个暗喻 严格意义上来说 我不觉得那算是 先生
- It's a metaphor. - I don't think it strictly is, sir.
从打比方的角度来说
As a figure of speech--
你就像一只充满火蚁的安全套一样令人讨厌
You know, you're about as annoying as a condom filled with fire ants.
这个他妈的暗喻怎么样?
How's that for a fucking metaphor?
那是个明喻 先生 闭上你的嘴 肥妞
- That's a simile, sir. - Shut your mouth, you fat girl.
那么你爸爸在哪个医院?
So what hospital is your dad in?
乔治·华盛顿医院
George Washington.
哦 那是个好医院
Oh, that's a good one.
那有个很大的星巴克
They got a big Starbucks there.
很不错 你知道的 去那的人们不...
It's nice. You know, people go in there that aren't--
你可以不用说话 谢谢
- You don't have to speak. - Thank you.
给你 女士 你尝尝
There you go, ma'am. You taste that.
那里就是天堂 这真大
- That's heaven right there. - This is big.
但我确信我能吃完
But I bet I can finish it.
我要四号洲际公路选区大胜 (摇摆选区 必争之地)
I want to smash the I-4 corridor--
我是说要完全的大胜 要全程专注在党内选举上
and I mean smash it-- all the while focusing on the inside game.
然后我们...我嘞个去
Then what-- holy cow.
一头猪
A pig.
这不是在直升机里
It's not being in the helicopter.
没关系 我可以乘直升机
That's fine. I can ride in a helicopter.
还只是刚刚进去而已 我就担心它会颠簸
It's just getting in. I'm afraid it's gonna wobble.
就像 你懂的 它就会把我的头
Like, you know, it'd chop the top of my head off
就像溏心蛋一样削下来  然后我就...
like a soft-boiled egg and then I'm, like,
会到处跑 试图把我的头放回去
running around trying to put my head back on.
这真疯狂 Mike 我只是写了篇影评
This is crazy, Mike. All I did was write a review of a movie.
我知道 Catherine 但是所有关于中东的事情都很糊涂
I know, Catherine, but the whole Middle East thing is very confusing.
对吗 Rahim?
Right, Rahim?
不 有时它对我来说是再清晰不过了
No, sometimes it can seem pretty clear-cut to me.
嗯 好吧 抱歉
Yeah, well-- excuse me.
Mike 你在哪? -
Mike, where are you?
我在烤猪的地方
I'm at the hog roast.
你是不是因为大脑萎缩而瘫痪了?
And are you paralyzed from the neck down?
你为什么没有阻止这个? 阻止...
- Why aren't you stopping this? - Stopping...
这一任内阁的态度有改变吗?
Has the position of this administration changed
对以色列和巴勒斯坦
toward Israel and Palestine?
当然 我们是支持以色列的...
We support the state of Israel, of course...
Mike 副总统正在谈团结
Mike, the VP is voicing solidarity
旋转的烤猪前跟犹太人
with the Jewish people in front of rotating pork.
...为犹太人 改变那个画面
- ...for the Jewish people. - Change the visual.
把那个画面弄走 是的 先生
- Deport the visual. - Yes, sir.
J-1-1.
你有什么Jonah紧急事件?
What's your Jonah emergency?
Jonah 让副总统离开那只猪
Jonah, move the veep away from the pig.
想想这里面的敏感性
Think about the sensitivities here.
什么 猪? Mike 这个国家 绝大部分的犹太人都不会对猪太在意
What, pork? Mike, most Jews in this country are fine with pork.
他们常说猪没什么的
Pork schmork, they often say.
这个国家的大部分犹太人
Most Jews in this country
都不会对猪太在意 Davison先生 猪肉没什么的 真的
are fine with pork, Mr. Davison. Pork schmork, really.
你听过旧约吗 Mike?
You ever hear of the Old Testament, Mike?
以色列 欧洲
Israel, Europe.
Jonah 以色列 欧洲
Jonah, Israel, Europe.
好吧 他妈的 好吧 Mike
Okay. Fuck. Fine, Mike.
但你他妈的欠我个人情 抱歉
But you fucking owe me for this. Excuse me.
这些养猪的不会问Selina中东政治什么的 对吧?
These pork folks won't ask Selina about Middle East politics, right?
哦 不 那些傻瓜大概认为
Oh, no. Those fuckers probably think
中东指的是堪萨斯吧
the Middle East means Kansas.
嘿 你知道吗? 我对疾病或者死亡
Hey, you know what? I'm not really great with illness
还有基本的安慰什么都不太在行
or death or basic empathy,
但我想说 关于你爸爸我感到很抱歉
but I just want to say I'm sorry about your dad
我认为你很勇敢
and I think you're being really brave.
什么?我们为什么停在这?
What? Why are we stopping here?
那是我爸
That's my dad.
天哪 他看起来可不像要死的样子
Jesus, he doesn't look like he's dying.
我家里用罪恶感来绑住我
My family was guilt-tripping the shit out of me
所以我把情况说夸张一点好来探访
and so I exaggerated to come visit.
除此之外 一个临死的爸爸是张免死金牌
Besides, a dying dad can be a get-out-of-jail-free card.
就像对Furlong的时候 喔
Like with Furlong. - Wow.
这真冷血
That is cold.
但是也很热辣
Also kind of hot.
...作为犹太人的祖国
...and as a homeland for the Jewish people
同时 我们也认为
while at the same time we support
巴勒斯坦人民需要一个稳定的家园
a settled homeland for the Palestinians.
我仍能看见那头猪的屁股
I can still see the pig's ass.
你没挡住 弯下身来
You're not blocking it. Bend down.
绑鞋带 随便什么
Tie your shoe, whatever.
那是个很似是而非的话题
That's a circle that's tricky to square.
总统和我…
And the president and I...
这种情形下我们很需要一个块头更大的人
We really need a bulkier man in this situation.
够了吗? 再靠近点
- Am I there? - Get closer towards it.
好吧 Mike 我已经紧挨着炭了
Okay, Mike, it's right next to the coals.
它们很烫
The coals are hot.
嘿 别碰那只猪
Hey, quit touching the pig.
这可不是他妈的爱畜动物园
It's not a fucking petting zoo.
女士 这关系国家安全 成吗?
Ma'am, this is a matter of security, okay?
你觉得这只猪会袭击她?
You think this pig is gonna attack her?
孩子那该死的已经被剥了皮 放在火上烤了
Son, that fucker is skinned and roasted.
那是个巨大的劣势
He's at a huge disadvantage.
好吧 瞧 总统办公室的 所以我呆定了
Okay, look, office of the president. So I'm staying.
我不关心是不是要出丧而占用那条街道
I don't care if there is a funeral procession due to use that street.
今天四点前它必须关闭
It is to be closed by 4:00 today.
那会让整个家庭都振奋起来 先生 人人都爱车队
It'll cheer the family up, sir. Everyone loves a motorcade.
您好 你想要什么?
Hello. What do you want?
你得不到 再见
You can't have it. Good-bye.
国会议员想在近几天内
The congressman would like to have
和副总统进行一次非常友好的谈话
a very polite chat in the next few days with the vice president.
不 他不能
No, he cannot.
我需要你去告诉副总统
I need you to let the veep know
我只是想
that I just wanted to apologize for any erratic behavior
为她之前所见的我的所有出格行为向她致歉
she might have witnessed from me in the past.
那些出格的行为是否包括
Does erratic behavior include you storming into this office
你冲进办公室然后大声地朝所有人吼?
and violently yelling at everyone?
是的 我失控了
Yes. I wasn't myself.
我有点粗暴
I was having a bit of a rough go.
我妻子 我并不是在寻求同情
My wife-- and I'm not looking for sympathy for this--
但她因为肾病十分虚弱
but she was very ill with kidney disease.
你的妻子很好 她刚跑了西雅图马拉松
Your wife is perfectly fine. She ran the Seattle Marathon.
好吧 别糊弄我 蜜糖
All right, don't fuck with me, honey.
把他妈的我的名字写到你那 愚蠢的时间表里面
Just put my fucking name in your stupid fucking schedule
让我见副总统!现在!
and get me a face-to-face with the veep now!
抱歉 你必须马上离开这里 先生
Excuse me. You need to leave this office now, sir.
我们得走了 哦 真的?
- We do need to leave. - Oh, really?
好吧 我有很多很多的关于Selina Meyer的档案盒
Okay, I've got boxes and boxes on Selina Meyer.
你听懂了吗?
You understand me?
我有他妈的关于她的潘多拉盒子
I've got Pandora's fucking boxes on her.
但我们正和某些你们党派的人的谎言抗争
But we're fighting the lies from many people in your party
那些关于我们做的事情对环境造成的影响的谎言
about the environmental impact of what we do.
要养猪可没法摆脱排泄物 女士
You can't raise pigs without excrement, ma'am.
啊哈 那是不可能做到的
- Uh-huh. - It just can't be done.
我明白 是的 它们排便
I see. Yes. - they defecate.
而且它们排便的速度很快
And they defecate with speed.
哦 上帝啊 哦 天哪 还排得不少
- Oh, Lord. Oh, goodness. - And volume.
好吧 我听到了 它们是猪
Well, I hear that. They're pigs.
那它们为什么不?我想听听其他人说的
Why wouldn't they? And I'm interested to hear a few other folks.
谢谢你花的时间 你好 美国小姐? 是的
- I thank you for your time. Hello, Miss America? - Yeah.
我已经挠了他妈的三个半小时的眉毛了
I've been scratching my eyebrow for three and a half fucking hours.
你去哪了 我以为我们不打算抓眉毛什么的
- Where have you been? - I thought we weren't doing the eyebrow thing.
你说了阴虱 好吧 从现在开始 我们挠眉毛
- You said about the crabs. - Okay, from now on, we're doing the eyebrow thing.
好吗?我们要离开这
Okay? And we've got to get out of here.
我说没说这个挠眉毛的主意是我女朋友出的?
Did I tell you my girlfriend came up with the eyebrow thing?
哦 好吧 那对她很好 我们得离开了 好吗?
Oh, well, good for her. We've got to go, right?
从中期选举开始 就开始多灾多难了
Since the midterms, it's been really apocalyptic.
我们知道你很忙 亲爱的 没关系
- We know you're busy, hon. - It's fine.
但是现在我的注意力全在你身上 爸爸
But right now I am focused on you, Daddy.
那是Dan Egan吗?
Is that Dan Egan?
所以你和你的女朋友讨论了我们的暗号?
So you discussed our signals with your girlfriend?
是的 她很有创造力
Yeah, she's really creative.
我认为她可以想出些不错的主意
I thought she could come up with some good ones.
她是你告诉的唯一的平民?
And is she the only civilian that you shared them with?
哦 是的女士 嗯哼
- Oh, yes, ma'am. - Uh-huh.
好吧 不哦 不 Dana不会泄露出去的
Well, no-- oh, no. Dana would not leak.
典型的第一阶段否认 (悲伤的五个阶段) 安静
classic first-stage denial. - quiet.
我是说 那肯定是 Gary 想想吧
I mean, it must be. Gary, think about it.
绝对是Dana
It must be Dana.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
她又管不住她的嘴了
She's getting her leak on.
他妈的这种可怕的味道是什么 Jonah?
What in the living fuck is that god-awful smell, Jonah?
哦 我夹克的某些地方浸透了猪油 女士
Oh, my jacket is partially soaked in pork fat, ma'am.
Oh.
所以你们两个后来没在一起?
So you two aren't back together, then?
不 不 只是同事
No, no. Just colleagues.
你伤了她的心 你知道吗? 没有的事
you broke Her heart. you know that? - No.
是 是的 不 他
- Yeah. Yes. - No. He--
他甚至没有触到它 我们只约会了三次
he didn't even graze it. We went on three dates.
哦 见鬼 Amy 你掏心掏得真快
Oh, dang, Amy. You put out quick.
Amy和我只是合不来
Amy and I just weren't compatible.
没错 我没法和我物种以外的人配对
Right. It turns out I can't mate with anyone outside of my species.
我们都知道你需要什么 Amy
We all know what you need, Amy.
我是指除了欠抽以外
I mean besides a big, fat slap.
我不想要孩子 好吗?
I do not want children, okay?
为什么没人能接受?
Why can nobody accept this?
甜心 你不需要现在做决定
Sweetie, you do not have to decide right now.
你的时间还很充裕
You still have plenty of time.
我一直到56岁都还能生 真厉害
- I remained fertile till I was 56. - Terrific.
就因为我有个阴道不代表我得把他们从那生出来... 看在上帝的面上 Amy
- Just because I have a vagina... - For God's sake, Amy.
我们只是希望你开心 甜心
We just want you to be happy, sweetie.
没有孩子我很开心
I am happy without kids.
我很开心 对吗? 哦 她极度开心
- I am-- right? - Oh, she's deliriously happy.
实际上工作的时候我们叫她亲切的Amy
At work we actually call her Amiable Amy.
我去买咖啡 还有人要吗?
I think I'm gonna go get a coffee. Anyone else?
不了 谢谢 我去帮你拿那第二杯咖啡
- No, thank you. - I will help you carry that second coffee.
我写了篇关于一部很重要的电影的论文
I wrote an essay about a very important film.
好吗? 你应该为我自豪
Okay? You should be proud of me.
又不是黛比大马士革 (臭名昭著的色情喜剧近似音）
It's not Debbie Does Damascus.
不 我很为你骄傲 但是 甜心
No, I am proud of you. But, sweetheart,
如果我们失去了那些亲以色列的选票
if we lose the pro-Israel vote,
那么两年后我们就会在佛罗里达败选
then we lose Florida in two years
那可是29张选举人票
and that's 29 electoral votes.
然后妈咪就会失业
And then Mommy's out of a job.
好吧 但我仍然不会道歉
Okay, I'm still not going to apologize.
你看过我说的那部电影吗?
Have you even seen the movie that I'm talking about?
我什么时候会有时间去看电影?
When would I have time to see a film?
我甚至没有看过那部很棒的
I haven't even been able to see
有蓝人的电影
that wonderful movie with the blue people in it.
阿凡达 阿凡达 就是那个
Avatar. - Avatar. Exactly.
所以你什么时候毕业?一年内?
So you graduate in what, a year?
是的 但愿吧 如果我能凑足
Yeah, hopefully, if I can get the money together
最后两学期的学费的话
for the last two semesters.
哦 银根紧张哈 嗯?
Ah, money's tight, huh?
你知道 我对钱的态度是...
You know, my attitude to money is--
我毕业的时候会是22岁 我有六万欠债
I'll be 22 when I graduate, I'll owe 60 grand.
我算过了 我都得背着这份学生贷款
And I did the math. I'll chase my student debt
之后的二十七年
for the next 27 years of my life.
嘿 这又有新鲜的咖啡了 如果有人想要的话
Hey, fresh coffee back here if you guys want some.
哦 棒极了 吔
Oh, great. Yeah.
咖啡
Coffee.
哦 天哪 哦 天哪
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
我欠了十万
I owe 100 grand.
我的个苍啊天啊
Sweet Jesus Christ.
我想去看那电影 我会去看那电影
I want to see the film and I will see the film.
Gary 我们要弄到这部片 叫五支歌 (1970电影)
Gary, we need to get it. It's Five Easy Pieces.
是5台破相机
It's 5 Broken Cameras.
好吧 破相机 好吧 妈妈 算了
- Okay, it's Broken Cameras. - Mom, don't even bother.
这就会像大号的我一样重头来过
This is gonna be like Super Size Me all over again.
你们为什么不干脆去看
Why don't you guys just go see Mamma Mia! again
他妈的第十遍妈妈咪呀?
for the 10th fucking time?
不许对我骂脏话 Catherine 不许
Do not swear at me, Catherine. Don't.
好吧 瞧 抱歉
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
我知道你感觉被抨击了 宝贝
I understand that you are feeling attacked, babe.
那就是我现在在这里和你一起的原因
And that's why I'm here with you right now.
我本来该出席国家安全会议的
I'm supposed to be at a national security meeting,
但你比较重要 好吗? 好吧
- but you are my priority, okay? - Okay.
你听到我说什么了吗 是的 我会道歉
- You hear what I'm saying? - Yeah, I'll apologize.
好女孩 如果我能和Rahim还有他家人一起过感恩节的话
good girl. - if I Can spend Thanksgiving with Rahim And his family.
不 亲爱的 外婆会来
No, darling. We've got Grandma coming.
我们要对她微笑然后切她的果冻 (感恩节传统食品)
We got to smile at her and cut her Jell-O.
是的 Sue?
Yeah, Sue?
Mike 如果她在厕所里 把她拖出来
Mike, if she's in the can, haul her out.
我不介意卫生纸是不是会黏在她屁股后
I don't care if she's trailing paper.
她只有现在出发才能赶到
She can make this if she leaves right this second.
她现在正和女儿在一起
She's currently with her daughter.
瞧 Mike 男人点 然后分清轻重缓急 成吗?
Look, Mike, man up and prioritize, okay?
我每天都干这个 决定轻重缓急 就这样
I do it every day. Prioritize, that is.
好吧
Okay.
周三怎么样 咳
What about Wednesday? - Ahem.
女士 你必须速度然后登上那架飞机
Ma'am, you need to make like a snake and get on that airplane.
好吧 但我正和
Okay, but I'm in the middle
我的女儿做很重要的谈话
of an important conversation with my daughter.
所以任何事都可以暂停 懂吗? 好吧
- So everything can be put on hold, okay? - Okay.
谢谢 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
所以我得和你还有外婆一起过感恩节
So I have to spend Thanksgiving with you and Memaw.
是的 周三
Yes. - Wednesday.
周三你得和你爸一起
Wednesday you're with your dad.
周四和我还有外婆
Thursday you're with me and Grandma.
周五你可以和你的新男朋友一起 好吗?
Friday you can be with the new boyfriend, okay?
还有周六
And Saturday.
如果你周六晚上回家的话可以
If you come home on Saturday night.
好 我去和Rahim说说看
Yeah, I'll check that over with Rahim.
好了 出发吧
Okay, let's get going.
你是个很棒的谈判家 我知道我是
you are a Great negotiator. - I know I am.
嘿 Sue打过电话
Hey. So Sue called.
很明显她给了Furlong一个大耳刮子
Apparently she bitch-slapped Furlong.
他总是得为此付出代价
He usually has to pay for that.
我们需要Catherine马上道歉
And we need that Catherine apology ASAP.
好吗?我可以做到 你可以留在这
Okay? I can do it, you can stay here.
我们用电邮保持联络
We'll liaise via e-mail.
唔 好 我真的
Um, yeah. I really--
实际上 你知道吗?如果
Actually, you know what? I would prefer it
你人能在那会更好
if you were physically there.
这 你知道的 是个很重要的声明
It's, you know, an important statement.
你是对的 那必须马上发生 走
You're right. It needs to happen. Let's go.
不客气
You're welcome.
亲切的Amy? 这就是你能想出的最好的称呼?
Amiable Amy? That is the best you could come up with?
啊 你知道的 我知道我该说白宫Amy
Yeah, you know, I knew I should have gone with Amy Whitehouse.
很高兴认识你...
It's very nice meeting you...
同样很高兴认识你 副总统女士
- It's so nice to meet you, too. - Madam Vice President.
没问题 你在学校学什么?
Sure. What are you studying at school?
计算机科学 辅修数学
Computer science. Math minor.
修那些你打算以后做什么?
Where are you headed with all that?
但愿 实际上 去政府的某个部门
Hopefully, actually, get into a government branch.
国防部或者联邦调查局 或许 啊 哼
- Defense or FBI, maybe. - Uh-huh.
好吧 我说波斯语 你会说波斯语?
- Well, I speak Farsi-- - You speak Farsi?
是的 但你在这出生?
Yeah. - But you were born here?
是的 我在这出生 唔嗯 不错
- Yes, I was born here. - Uh-huh, great.
你父母也是这出生的?
And your parents were born here?
实际上他们是在伊朗的德黑兰出生的
They were actually born in Iran in Tehran.
是的 他们是从那来的
Yeah, that's where we're from.
哦 明白了 德黑兰 是的 没错
- Oh, I see. Tehran. - Yeah. Yep.
女士 五角大楼的Mercer将军打来电话
Ma'am, General Mercer from the Pentagon is on the phone.
哦 我现在不需要和Mercer将军谈话
Oh, I don't need to talk to General Mercer right now.
他很急切 我现在不需要他的电话
- He's pretty insistent. - I don't need a General Mercer call right now.
他真的在线上 -
He's really on the phone.
哦 Mercer将军在线上
- Oh, General Mercer's on the phone. - Mm-hmm.
你能稍等一会吗 Rahim?
Can you hang tight two seconds, Rahim?
Mercer将军 我很抱歉我得打这通电话 副总统女士
- General Mercer. - I'm sorry to be calling, Madam Vice President,
但我们正准备
but we are going to be discussing
在25分钟后讨论人质情况
the hostage situation in around 25 minutes.
你觉得你能赶到 还是我们该在你缺席的情况下直接讨论?
Do you think you can get here or should we go ahead without you?
不 不 不 别在我到之前进行
No, no, no. Don't go ahead without me.
我们可以在飞机里做视频连线 我去处理 没问题
- We can set up a video link from the plane. - I'm on it. I got it.
那么那样应该可以很完美地解决问题
So that would work out perfectly.
我希望Rahim能留下来 我得 唔唔
And I want Rahim to stay. I've got to-- mm-hmm.
Rahim 呆在这 你也一样 Catherine 是的 好吧
- Rahim, stay. You, too, Catherine. - Yeah, okay.
谢谢 副总统女士 谢谢
- Thank you, Madam Vice President. - Thank you.
事实上我们或许该走了
We should actually probably go.
我得回去为期中考试学习了
I have to get back to study for a midterm.
是的 是的 你父母的名字是?
Yeah, yeah. What are your parents' names?
那个Rahim看起来是个不错的男孩 是的 女士
- That Rahim turns out to be a nice boy. - Yes, ma'am.
给他和他的全家做一个安全检查
Let's run a security check on him and his entire family.
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
调查他们的财务状况 是的 女士
- And investigate their finances. - Yes, ma'am.
实际上我之前就在重新思考我的财务状况
I was actually reconsidering my financial situation.
哦 你打算问我要钱吗 Mike?
Oh, are you about to ask me for money, Mike?
我没这么想 不 不 不
- I don't want to. - No, no, no.
我认为你是而且我想给你钱
I thought you would and I want to give you money.
而且我有这笔钱 那为什么不?
And I have the money, so why not?
没错 而且那不多
Exactly. And it's not a big--
给我的传媒主任现金
Giving cash to my director of communications--
你觉得这样没问题么 Mike?
do you think that that would play well, Mike?
是的 不 不 不行
- Yeah. - No. No, it wouldn't.
不 女士
No, ma'am.
我没法像这样进行视频会议
I can't videoconference like this.
我压根没法摆脱这个压痕
I can't get the dent out at all.
我看起来像个恶心的小丑 你想让我解决这个问题吗?
I Look Like Bozo. - do you want me to fix it?
哦 你有吹风机吗? 没有
- Oh, do you have a blow-dryer? - I don't.
没有 这个帽子是谁的主意?
No. Whose idea was this hat?
也是Dana的主意? 不是
- Was that Dana's idea, too? - Mm-mm.
你和她说过话了? 我们短信联络过
Did you talk to her? - We texted.
还有呢? 她
- And? - She--
她可能提过暗号的事情
she may have mentioned the signals
向她的某个女朋友
to one of her girlfriends.
视频会议的连接已经好了 女士
The link to your video conference is up, ma'am.
Gary...
我不想这么说
I do not like to say this,
但是你今天实在是让我太失望了
but you have truly disappointed me today.
你知道你今天让我看起来有多蠢吗
Do you have any idea how foolish you have made me look?
我知道
I do.
我度过了最好的一天
I am having the best day.
真是一段美好的时光
This is such a great time.
我们在空军二号上 美国嘿正式开始了
We're on Air Force Two. U.S. Hey is getting started.
伙计们 我们挽救了佛罗里达的选票
Guys, we saved the Florida vote.
你们想玩一下iPad的拼字游戏吗?
You guys want to play iPad Scrabble?
Jonah 麻烦 闭嘴
Jonah, please. Just shut up.
Mike 你想...
Mike, you want to...
把我夹克上的猪油吸出来吗?
suck some of the pork fat out of my jacket?
来吧 这可是免费的大餐
Come on, it's a free meal.
嘿 Lori   Kent Davison还来这吗?
Hey, Lori. Does Kent Davison still come here?
不 他离开了
No, he left.
他说这里特区的人太多了什么的
He said it was too full of DC people or something.
我看到昨天你被战术手册提到了
I see you got a mention in Playbook yesterday.
是的 真棒
Yep. - Awesome.
我给你的名字设定了谷歌警报
I have a Google alert set up for your name.
哦 你看了邮报上Krauthammer
- Wow. - Hey, did you catch Krauthammer
关于人质情况的文章么?
in the Post about the hostage situation?
你是那个总是在停车库里向我问好的人吗?
Are you the guy that always says hi to me in the garage?
没错
Yeah.
哦 我得去举一会他妈的哑铃
Yeah, I got to do some fucking weights.
这是给迟钝的蠢货们用的
This is for rubber idiots.